[{"answer": "What happened to the car", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, yeah, it'll kill me", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah, it'll kill me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I must know", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I don't know! How am I supposed to know?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "*", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "All bald people look good in hats", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What a bald paradise that must have been. Nobody knew", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I went to look in the mirror, it wasn't there. You threw off my equilibrium", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I can't drive", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You don't understand. A garage. I can't even pull in there. It's like going to a prostitute. Why should I pay, when if I apply myself, maybe I could get it for free?  What? What do you want? Go around me, I'm looking for spaces", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh beautiful! Look at that, the dream space right in front of my friend's building. Huh? Dreams can come true, what did I tell you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend, wait, you don't know who this guy is, people kill for a parking space in this city", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend? my friend gets out of the car to confront the other driver", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I can if I have room", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, I'm not gonna move the car", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Do you believe this guy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I am not putting it in a garage, it's my space", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Is that my friend? my friend?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yeah, I know my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Why should anything be wrong", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Me? You see what he did here, you see how he tried to sneak into my space", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You only went in front first 'cause you saw me backing up and you didn't have room to parallel park", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hey, just 'cause I went in front first doesn't mean I'm sneaking in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I only went in front first 'cause I could make it in front first and if you pull out I'll show you", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't believe it, what did you say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A pack of teenagers", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No no, I never said I was a good driver, I said I was a good parker", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend, I never said driver, I said parker, a great parker", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No you weren't. Stop there, that's fine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Do you", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "He could have pulled up to the car and backed in, but he chose to go in head first", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No he wasn't", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No he couldn't, because the other car was already backing in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "All that matters is who was there first", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No, I'm not pregnant", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No, I'm not pregnant", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yes, I'm sure", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "He thinks you're a phony", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I can't, I told my friend I was vaulting it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Open my vault", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You gotta open the vault", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Open your vault", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Open my vault", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Once I open the vault, it ceases to be a vault", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Man, that my friend is so phony.  Why'd you tell him?!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Parking-Space.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "He begged you?", "qsentId": 50}]